(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.1",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-pro-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights during the performance.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
ATTENTION ご来場のお客様へ 演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください 声出し応援OKです
ATTENTION To visiting guests: Please be aware of flashing lights. Cheering loudly is OK.
どアニメ宣言！
Do-Anime Declaration!
アニメにハマって 歌いたくなっちゃった
I got hooked on anime, and now I want to sing.
推しのシーン見ながらカラオケ歌えるなんて
Being able to sing karaoke while watching scenes of my fave...
尊すぎてツライ！
It's so precious it hurts!
歌いたいアニメ・ゲームソング見つけよう！
Let's find anime and game songs we want to sing!
JOYSOUND！
JOYSOUND!
ReGLOSS 2nd Album「Snapshot」のレコードとカセットテープが
ReGLOSS 2nd Album 'Snapshot' vinyl records and cassette tapes...
2026年2月25日よりHMV限定で発売決定しました！
...will be released exclusively at HMV starting February 25, 2026!
12月17日いっぱいまでにご予約いただくと、
If you reserve by the end of December 17th...
期間限定予約特典としてスマホサイズステッカーをプレゼント！
...you'll receive a smartphone-sized sticker as a limited-time bonus!
さらに抽選で5名様にサイン入りポスターをプレゼント！
Plus, 5 lucky winners will receive a signed poster!
HMV ReGLOSS レコード カセットで検索！
Search for HMV ReGLOSS Record Cassette!
以上！
That's all!
ReGLOSSでした〜！！
This was ReGLOSS~!!
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
ATTENTION: ご来場のお客様へ
ATTENTION: To our guests
演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください
Please be aware of flashing lights.
声出し応援OKです
Cheering loudly is OK.
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ATTENTION: 演出の都合上、照明の点滅にご注意ください / 声出し応援OKです
ATTENTION: Please be aware of flashing lights. / Cheering loudly is OK.
本日は ReGLOSS 1st Live “Flashpoint” にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much for coming to ReGLOSS 1st Live "Flashpoint" today!
Reach the top!
We are...
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To ensure you enjoy the live show until the end, we have a few announcements.
公演中の撮影・録音・録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
The use of photography, recording, and video equipment during the performance is strictly prohibited.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は無理をせず、近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you happen to feel unwell, please do not push yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を...
Moshing, diving, jumping high, throwing objects onto the stage...
ステージに、も、も...
Onto the stage... th-th...
大丈夫？大丈夫だよ
Are you okay? It's okay.
すいませんね！あの、収録とかじゃないんでね！
Sorry about that! Uh, it's not like this is a recording or anything!
緊張してるね
She's nervous.
緊張してます、ごめんなさい、もう一回やらせてくださいごめんなさい！
I'm nervous, I'm sorry! Please let me do it one more time, sorry!
休み休みね、みんなの声もあるからね
Take your time, everyone's cheering for you.
えー、会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、ステージに物を投げ込むなど、
Um, moshing, diving, jumping high, throwing objects onto the stage,
他の、みんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
and any other acts that cause trouble for others or interfere with the performance are strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and have a blast!
抹茶！
Matcha!
本公演は、映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
This performance will have cameras for video streaming and photography, and the audience may be captured.
映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、予めご了承ください。
Please note that the footage and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
委員長！
Chairperson!
ライブのハッシュタグは、#ReGLOSS1stLive です！
The hashtag for the live concert is #ReGLOSS1stLive!
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてください！
Use the hashtag and hype it up a lot!
それでは開演までもう少々...
Well then, just a little longer until the show starts...
盛り上がる準備はできてますかー！
Are you ready to get hype?!
Yeah!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がろうー！
Let's all get hype together!
以上、ReGLOSSでした！
That's all from ReGLOSS!
上機嫌に Play the wake up people
In a good mood, play the wake up, people.
描く計画で Get a 希望
Get a hope with the plan we draw.
どんなシーズンも駆けつけ Pretty good OK
Rushing to any season, pretty good, OK.
1人じゃ足りない この声より
More than this voice that isn't enough alone.
The sounds force 頂の私 Command C
The sounds force, me at the summit, Command C.
何も消さない...
I won't erase anything...
いつもそばにいるけれど
I'm always by your side, but...
妙に面白い風変わり
Strangely interesting and eccentric.
胸踊る巡り合いは一期一会
This heart-pounding encounter is a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
偶然の...
A coincidence's...
全部ひっさげて包み込む
Carrying everything and wrapping it up.
Flashpoint!
移ろい色褪せるように
Like changing and fading colors.
秘密の奥...
Deep in the secret...
春が来た パッと桜舞う
Spring has come, suddenly cherry blossoms dance.
Show timeで儚いね 笑って Enjoy
It's show time and it's fleeting, so smile and enjoy.
踊ってみた様 アルゴリズムの中
Like I tried dancing inside the algorithm.
ちょっと背伸びして
Stretching a little.
酔いが覚めるまで
Until I sober up.
この世界を
This world...
塗り替えるとは
to repaint it.
きっと信じないけど
Surely you won't believe it, but...
君の中の世界なら変えられるはず
If it's the world inside you, it should be changeable.
根付いて咲いて実って枯れて
Take root, bloom, bear fruit, and wither.
何ひとつ無駄じゃないから
Because not a single thing is a waste.
最高に君が笑ってくれれば
If you just smile your best...
もうそれだけでいい
that alone is enough.
Otonose Kanade
Ichijou Ririka
Juufuutei Raden
Todoroki Hajime
Flashpoint
My heart starts skipping a beat
紐解いた新章
A new chapter has been unraveled
様変わりしてく Show time
The show time is completely changing
全然悪くないイマジネーション
An imagination that's not bad at all
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The mist in my vision clears up
悲しみに別れを告げる
Bidding farewell to sadness
酸いも甘いも宙に放り出して
Throwing both sourness and sweetness into the air
滲む空 インクは薔薇色
The bleeding sky, the ink is rose-colored
どれだけ上手く魅せようとしても
No matter how well I try to show it off
キミがいなければ何の意味もない
Without you, it means nothing
擦り傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion that won't even leave a scratch
針の落ちないレコードさ
It's a record where the needle never drops
たった今とめどない追い風背にして
Right now, with an endless tailwind at our backs
Come on Let's roll
颯爽と吹き荒れる向かい風にも
Even against the dashing headwind that rages
心なびかせて
Let our hearts flutter
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on to the future
Flying したって alright restart the life
Even if we're flying, alright, restart the life
ときめいてしまえば
If you just let your heart flutter
瞬く間に広がる解放区
The liberated zone spreads in the blink of an eye
一つ一つ全てがドラマ
One by one, everything is a drama
待ちわびた daybreak restart the life
The awaited daybreak, restart the life
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
A panorama that changes and colors in turn
満ち溢れる feeling 奏ででしょう
We'll play this overflowing feeling
始まりの
The time for
その時が来た
the beginning has come
何故何故 impossible
Why, why impossible?
目を覚ます
Waking up to
まだ誰も知らない世界
a world that no one knows yet
互換してるだけじゃ味気ない
It's dull if we're just compatible
Real time で通じ合って
Connecting in real time
振り子にかける motion
Motion applied to the pendulum
後の祭りでも I don't mind
I don't mind even if it's too late
感情的なシチュエーション
An emotional situation
行けるとこまで行ってみたい
I want to go as far as I can
選択肢にない get away
'Get away' isn't among the choices
共に声を鳴らせ
Let our voices ring out together
肌を貫くような真っ直ぐな痛みが
A straight pain that feels like it pierces the skin
伴っても
Even if it comes with it
その仲間たちと最果てまで
To the very end with these friends
Keep running to the end
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on to the future
Flying したって alright restart the life
Even if we're flying, alright, restart the life
ときめいてしまえば
If you just let your heart flutter
瞬く間に広がる解放区
The liberated zone spreads in the blink of an eye
一つ一つ全てがドラマ
One by one, everything is a drama
待ちわびた daybreak restart the life
The awaited daybreak, restart the life
代わる代わる彩るパノラマ
A panorama that changes and colors in turn
満ち溢れる feeling 奏ででしょう
We'll play this overflowing feeling
飛び出せ you with me yeah
Jump out, you with me yeah
恐れるものはない restart the life
There's nothing to fear, restart the life
見え透いた言い訳が
Transparent excuses
通用しなくなった訳は
no longer work because
Restart the life
皆さん こんにちは！
Hello everyone!
ReGLOSS 1st Live Flashpoint へようこそいらっしゃいました！
Welcome to ReGLOSS 1st Live Flashpoint!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
本日は皆さん
Everyone, for today,
楽しんで行って素敵な一日に致しましょう！
let's have fun and make it a wonderful day!
ReGLOSS は Number One をお届け致します！
ReGLOSS will deliver number one!
盛り上がって行きましょう！
Let's get hyped!
みんな！次の曲は「Easy Peasy」だよ！
Everyone! The next song is 'Easy Peasy'!
盛り上がる準備はいいですか？
Are you ready to get hyped?
みんなで Oki-Doki してね！
Let's do Oki-Doki together!
Oki Doki 調子最高 on the beat
Oki Doki, feeling the best on the beat
Easy breezy 歌い出せば my favorite
Easy breezy, once we start singing, it's my favorite
Oki Doki そのままでいたいよね
Oki Doki, I want to stay just like this
Easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance everybody
それぞれ異なる価値観
Everyone has different values
そんなのそんなのそれノリも
That, that, even that groove
笑い飛ばせば問題ないって
If you laugh it off, there's no problem
勝った方が勝ちの決まりない
There's no rule that the winner takes all
いつから始まる？
When does it start?
ゆっくりなのが my pace
Slow is my pace
気づけばハマってる
Before I knew it, I was hooked
無駄話も一時パス
Pass on the idle chatter for a moment
ちょっと WAIT!
Just a WAIT!
運命共同体
We're in this together
伝染していく喜怒哀楽
Infectious emotions spreading
分かち合えるワタシ
I can share this
共に目指すは
Aiming together to
Reach the top! Yeah!
絶対絶対絶対絶対
Absolute, absolute, absolute, absolute
的キラーチューン
killer tune
今は自由気まま
Right now, free and easy,
水入らずの universe
our private universe
リンドンリンドンリンドン進行するシナプス
Ring-dong, ring-dong, ring-dong, synapses progressing
限界突破惹きつける miracle
Breaking limits, attracting a miracle
みんな見える？
Can you see everyone?
みんなのことよく見えてますよ！
I can see everyone very well!
次はもっとブンブン振ってけ！
Next, wave them even more vigorously!
Oki Doki 調子最高 on the beat
Oki Doki, feeling the best on the beat
Easy breezy 歌い出せば my favorite
Easy breezy, once we start singing, it's my favorite
Oki Doki そのままでいたいよね
Oki Doki, I want to stay just like this
Easy breezy 踊ろうよ everybody
Easy breezy, let's dance everybody
一人募ればまた一人
If one gathers, then another one
一緒に味わいたい気持ち
The feeling of wanting to taste it together
溢れ出すみんなのモノローグ
Everyone's monologue overflowing
共鳴する鼓動が
The resonating heartbeat...
操作不可能なメモリー
...is an uncontrollable memory.
運命...
Destiny...
宣戦布告
A declaration of war.
Reach the top Yeah!
絶対 絶対 絶対 絶対的キラーチューン
An absolutely, absolutely, absolute killer tune.
Imma watch you 一番の
Imma watch you, the number one...
Okey Dokey 調子最高 Otherwise
Okey Dokey, feeling great, otherwise...
Easy Breezy 大好き
Easy Breezy, I love it.
Favorite
Okey Dokey
このままでいたいよね
I want to stay like this.
Easy Breezy
踊ろうよ Everybody
Let's dance, Everybody!
ReGLOSS 1st Live...
Flashpoint へようこそ！
...Welcome to Flashpoint!
ようこそ〜！
Welcome!
いつもの挨拶からいきましょう！
Let's start with our usual greeting!
Reach the top, we are...
ReGLOSS！
ReGLOSS!
では早速、自己紹介からしていきたいと思います！
Now, I'd like to start with self-introductions right away!
音の奏では〜？
Playing the sound is...?
奏〜！
Kanade!
奏でること、音乃瀬奏です！
I'm Otonose Kanade!
ホロライブデバイス、ReGLOSSの音楽家の卵...
Hololive Device, ReGLOSS's musician-in-training...
奏でること、音乃瀬奏です！
I'm Otonose Kanade!
みんな会えて嬉しいよ〜！
I'm so happy to see everyone!
みんなになってる！ありがとう！
Wait, everyone's turning into that?! Thank you!
そして！
And next!
可愛い、ポジティブ、
Cute, positive...
ジーニアス！
Genius!
莉々華です！
It's Ririka!
一条莉々華だよ〜！
I'm Ichijo Ririka!
ヤバい、もうみんなの声めっちゃ...
Oh my god, everyone's voices are so...
全身で浴びてる今！
...washing over my whole body right now!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
最高の気分！そして？
Best feeling ever! And next?
はい、ホロライブデバイス、ReGLOSSの賑やかし担当...
Yes, Hololive Device, ReGLOSS's hype person...
儒烏風亭一門、前座見習い...
Apprentice of the Juufutei school...
儒烏風亭らでんでございます。
I am Juufutei Raden.
本日はどうぞよろしくお願い申し上げます。
It is a pleasure to be here today.
最後は〜？
And last is?
はい、ブーンブーン！
Yes, boom boom!
ホロライブデバイス、ReGLOSSの番長...
Hololive Device, ReGLOSS's Bancho...
轟はじめです！
I'm Todoroki Hajime!
みんなさん、こんちくわ〜！
Kon-chikuwa, everyone!
こんちくわ〜！
Kon-chikuwa!
紫ありがと〜！
Thanks for the purple lights!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ついに始まりました！
It's finally started!
ReGLOSS 1st Live！
ReGLOSS 1st Live!
会場は... ここ！
The venue is... here!
有明アリーナ！
Ariake Arena!
こんなにたくさんのGLOSSARが集まってくれました！
So many GLOSSARs have gathered here!
すごい！もう最高の景色ですよ！
Amazing! This is the best view ever!
皆さんありがとうございます！
Thank you so much, everyone!
思い思いのね、ファッションとかもね。
All your unique outfits too.
そう！目で見えてね。
Right! I can see them.
Feelin' Graduationの時ちょっとテンションが爆上がりしてしまいましたけれども。
My excitement exploded during 'Feelin' Graduation'.
本当にありがとうございます。
Thank you so much.
今日は最後まで思いっきり楽しんで参りましょう！
Let's enjoy ourselves to the fullest until the very end today!
お願いしま〜す！
Let's do this!
そしてね！
Also!
会場だけじゃなくて、配信もされております！
It's not just the venue, we're also streaming!
配信のみなたん楽しんでますか〜！
Is everyone on the stream having fun?!
配信のみなたんも〜！
Everyone on the stream too!
コメントもね！
The comments too!
そしてそして！
And, and!
韓国ではライブビューイングが実施されています！
Live viewing is being held in Korea!
アニョハセヨ〜！
Annyeonghaseyo!
ライブビューイングをご覧の皆さん、楽しんでますか〜？
Is everyone watching the live viewing having fun?
すごい！
Amazing!
奏、喋れた！
Kanade, you spoke it!
当たり前だろ！
Of course I did!
はい、ということで早速ですが...
Yes, so moving right along...
今立っているこのステージではなく...
...not this stage we're standing on now...
なんと2階からの登場でございましたが、皆さんびっくりした？
...but we appeared from the second floor! Were you surprised?
どうだった？
How was it?
びっくりした〜？
Surprised?
オープニングから Feelin' Graduation
From the opening with 'Feelin' Graduation'...
そして Buddies と
...and then 'Buddies'...
2曲続けてお披露目させていただきましたが
...we performed two songs in a row.
皆さんいかがでしたか？
How did you like them?
どうよどうよ〜！
How was it, how was it?!
そしてね、みなたんもお気づきかと思いますけども
And, as I think everyone has noticed...
今回のライブは...
...for this concert...
バンドメンバーと一緒にお届けしています！
...we're bringing it to you with our band members!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
かっこいい！
So cool!
普段聴いてるあの曲が
Those songs you usually listen to...
どんなアレンジになるのか
...how will they be arranged?
お楽しみに！
Look forward to it!
今日の感想や心に残った瞬間は、
Your thoughts on today and memorable moments...
ハッシュタグ #ReGLOSS_1stLive で
...please use the hashtag #ReGLOSS_1stLive...
ぜひポストしてください！
...and definitely post them!
みんなの感想、後で我々見に行きますので
We'll go look at everyone's comments later...
めちゃくちゃ楽しみです！
...so we're really looking forward to it!
よろしくお願いします！
Please do!
お願いします！
Please!
それでは
So then...
早速ではございますが
...it's a bit sudden, but...
次の曲に行きましょうか？
...shall we go to the next song?
あ、でも待って待って！
Ah, but wait, wait!
YouTubeやTikTokで見てくれてる皆さん
Everyone watching on YouTube and TikTok...
ごめんなさい！
...I'm sorry!
次の曲で最後となっております！
The next song will be the last one!
いい？
Is that okay?
まだまだ一緒に盛り上がりたいみんなは、概要欄のリンクから見てください！
Everyone who wants to keep partying with us, please check the link in the description!
はーい！
Yeaaaah!
みなちゃーん！ライブはね、まだまだ始まったばかりでちゅよ！
Everyone! The live has only just begun!
最後までね、一緒に最高の時間を作ろう！
Let's create the best time together until the very end!
おー！
Yeah!
Snow fall
触れる上空
Touching the upper sky
幻想と過ち
Illusions and mistakes
ノイズは砂嵐
Noise is a sandstorm
Slo-mo
Come let me show you
戯けてみせる銀世界 Yeah yeah yeah yeah
The silver world acting funny, yeah yeah yeah yeah
If the sky is falling down
If the stars had no shine
真っさらな紙の上
On a blank sheet of paper
答え滲ませる
Letting the answer blur
すべて思うままに
Everything as I wish
風が刻む 波の Melody
The melody of waves carved by the wind
Pandora Pandora ユメヲ Holding in my heart
Pandora, Pandora, holding dreams in my heart
移ろい 色褪せぬように
So it changes but never fades
Pandora Pandora 秘密のオブジェ SKAVLA
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object, SKAVLA
SKAVLA Rum pum pum pum pum pum pum pum
象る STAR SKAVLA
Modeling STAR SKAVLA
灯す光 The sign of sprouting SKAVLA
The lighting light, the sign of sprouting SKAVLA
ワンクールのドラマよりも永い Fairy tale
A fairy tale longer than a one-cour drama
嘘偽りなく Take this pain
Without lies or falsehoods, take this pain
匙を投げた Plastic mind
A plastic mind that gave up
この世にオモテもウラもない
There is no front or back in this world
いつも違う表情 朧げな Irony
Always different expressions, faint irony
一日を抱き締めてたいのに
Even though I want to embrace the day
沈む足跡
Sinking footprints
怯む暇はない 上を目指そう
No time to flinch, let's aim for the top
In a world where no one's hurt
I might not have become kind
忍ばせて、仮初
Hide it, transient
朽ちるまで待ち惚け
Waiting in vain until it rots
いずれ花になる
Eventually it will become a flower
風が刻む 波の Melody
The melody of waves carved by the wind
Pandora Pandora ユメヲ Holding in my heart
Pandora, Pandora, holding dreams in my heart
移ろい 色褪せぬように
So it changes but never fades
Pandora Pandora 秘密のオブジェ
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object
可能性が Swirling in a dance
Possibilities swirling in a dance
幾層にも重なって
Layered many times
たゆたう歪に Ambivalence
Ambivalence in the swaying distortion
振り解いた その向かい風
That headwind I shook off
SKAVLA Rum pum pum pum pum！！
SKAVLA Rum pum pum pum pum!!
今こそ 切なる願い 打ち鳴らせ Wake up
Now is the time, earnest wish, ring it out, Wake up
そっと手を伸ばす 冬枯れの結晶
Softly reach out hand, winter-withered crystal
閉ざしてしまいそうな夜だって
Even on nights that seem about to close up
この歌声で繋ぎとめてみせるから
I'll show you I can tie it together with this singing voice
風が刻む 波の Melody
The melody of waves carved by the wind
Pandora Pandora ユメヲ Holding in my heart
Pandora, Pandora, holding dreams in my heart
移ろい 色褪せぬように
So it changes but never fades
Pandora Pandora 秘密のオブジェ SKAVLA
Pandora, Pandora, a secret object, SKAVLA
Rum pum pum pum pum pum pum pum
SKAVLA Rum pum pum pum pum pum pum pum
象る STAR SKAVLA
Modeling STAR SKAVLA
灯す光 The sign of sprouting SKAVLA
The lighting light, the sign of sprouting SKAVLA
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
ご視聴ありがとうございました！
Thank you for watching!